Guide to the Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 1, Section 1: Boxes 1-22
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 1, Section 1: Boxes 1-22
- Box: 13, Folder: 4 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Program for Self-Development for Employees, Publication (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Box: 13, Folder: 5 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: A Profile of Textiles, Publication (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: How Textiles are Made, Publication (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: Curriculum Related Educational Materials about Textiles, Publication (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: The Wonderful New World of Textiles, Publication (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: 101 Durable Press, Publication (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Item 6: Textiles From Start to Finish, Publication (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Item 7: There's a Career for you inTextile Manufacturing, Publication (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Item 8: Career Awareness through Textiles, Publication (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Item 9: There's a Career for you inTextile Administration, Publication (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Item 10: There's a Career for you inTextile Marketing and Merchandising, Publication (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Item 11: There's a College for you inTextiles, Publication (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Item 12: There's a Career for you inTextile International Business, Publication (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Item 13: There's a Career for you inTextile Research and Development, Publication (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Item 14: There's a Career for you inTextile Environmental Sciences, Publication (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Item 15: ATMI, Publication (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Item 16: Ten Years of Cotton Textiles, Publication (Box 13, Folder 5)
    By John L. Severance. Item is in English.
- Box: 13, Folder: 6 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Facts You Will Want to Know about Your Job, Publication (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: Personnel File, Publication (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Box: 13, Folder: 7 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Retirement Plan, Publication (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: Your Group Insurance, Publication (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Box: 13, Folder: 8 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: The Place of Trade Association in the National Economy, Publication (Box 13, Folder 8)
    By Charles Sawyer. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Who Best Represents Business in Washington, Publication (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Item 3: How Trade Assocs. Contribute to The Profitable Operation of Business, Publication (Box 13, Folder 8)
    By US Chamber of Commerce. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Trade Assocs in the United States, Publication (Box 13, Folder 8)
    By Jay Judkins. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: A Challenge, Publication (Box 13, Folder 8)
    By Clem D. Johnston. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: President's Committee on Business and Government, Publication (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Item 7: Toward Better Employee Relations, Publication (Box 13, Folder 8)
    By Roscoe C. Edlund. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Trends in Manufacturing, Publication (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Item 9: The Do's and Don'ts of Conventions, Publication (Box 13, Folder 8)
    By Rudolph J. Blais. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Participation in the War Program, Publication (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Item 11: Trade Associations and the Future, Publication (Box 13, Folder 8)
    By George P. Lamb. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Legal Responsibilities of Trade Assoc Execs, Publication (Box 13, Folder 8)
    By Edward R. Johnston. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Legislative Responsibilities of Trade Assoc Execs, Publication (Box 13, Folder 8)
    By J.T. Meek. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Stimulating Membership Participation, Publication (Box 13, Folder 8)
    By S.B. Shapiro. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Community Development Service; Vol 2 No. 5, Publication (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Item 16: Management's Responsibility to Capitalism, Publication (Box 13, Folder 8)
    By Paul G. Hoffman. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: ATAE PR Reporter; Vol 1-3, Publication (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Item 18: Let's Look at Business, Publication (Box 13, Folder 8)
    By Ralph Bradford. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: Legislation Affecting Trade Associations, Publication (Box 13, Folder 8)
    By Joseph M. Gambatese. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: Presentation of 1948 Awards, Publication (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Item 21: ATAE Comt. On Office Management and Practices, Publication (Box 13, Folder 8)
    By Reuben C. Ball. Item is in English.
  - Item 22: Memo on Cement Institute Basing Point Case, Publication (Box 13, Folder 8)
    By Charles A. Horsky. Item is in English.
  - Item 23: You've a Business Stake in Civic Clubs, Publication (Box 13, Folder 8)
    By Russell D. Lund. Item is in English.
  - Item 24: Insurance Activities of Trade Assns. 1947, Publication (Box 13, Folder 8)
    By Chester A. Kline. Item is in English.
  - Item 25: 1950 Will be Important, Publication (Box 13, Folder 8)
    By Albert Johnson. Item is in English.
  - Item 26: Better Relations Between Business, Education and Young People, Publication (Box 13, Folder 8)
    By G. Edward Pendray. Item is in English.
  - Item 27: A Critical Analysis of the Opportunities for Trade Assoc. Leadership, Publication (Box 13, Folder 8)
    By Elmo Roper. Item is in English.
  - Item 28: What Future for ATAE, Publication (Box 13, Folder 8)
    By Wesley Hardenbergh. Item is in English.
  - Item 29: The Post-War Trade Assoc., Publication (Box 13, Folder 8)
    By Harry B. Lindsay. Item is in English.
  - Item 30: How Universities can Serve Trade Assocs. And Industry, Publication (Box 13, Folder 8)
    By Fred J. Fagg. Item is in English.
  - Item 31: Cooperation with Educational Institutions, Publication (Box 13, Folder 8)
    By Dr. C.C. Balderston. Item is in English.
  - Item 32: Keep that Membership, Publication (Box 13, Folder 8)
    By Frank G. Steinebach. Item is in English.
  - Item 33: Summarization of Proceedings of ATAE Spring Meeting, Publication (Box 13, Folder 8)
    By Robert W. Paine. Item is in English.
  - Item 34: Future Labor Problems, Publication (Box 13, Folder 8)
    By Samuel M. Fisher. Item is in English.
  - Item 35: Meeting Check List, Publication (Box 13, Folder 8)
    By Walter S. Doxsey. Item is in English.
  - Item 36: Today's Opportunity for Trade Assocs., Publication (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Item 37: Opportunity for Trade Assocs., Publication (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Item 38: The Legal Aspects of Trade Assoc. Cooperation with the Capehart Comt., Publication (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Item 39: We Salute the Trade Assoc's Economic Statesman, Publication (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Item 40: Trade Assoc's Bulletins and Publications, Publication (Box 13, Folder 8)
    By Reuel W. Elton. Item is in English.
  - Item 41: Here are 10 Ways to State a Meeting on Time, Publication (Box 13, Folder 8)
    By George K. Dahl. Item is in English.
  - Item 42: The Responsibility of Business under the Anti-Trust Laws, Publication (Box 13, Folder 8)
    By John A. Logan. Item is in English.
  - Item 43: Trade Association's Place in Public Relations, Publication (Box 13, Folder 8)
    By Robert E. Harper. Item is in English.
  - Item 44: Assoc Presidents, Publication (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Item 45: Summary of Developments under Labor-Management Relations Act, Publication (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Item 46: The Journal of Accountancy, Publication (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Item 47: Suggested Procedure for Subject Comts. To Aid in Increasing ATAE Services, Publication (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Item 48: The Business Outlook, Publication (Box 13, Folder 8)
    By Walter Hoadley, Jr. Item is in English.
  - Item 49: ATAE Constitution and By-Laws, Publication (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Item 50: Who Profits from Profits?, Publication (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Item 51: 35 Ways to Kill an Assoc., Publication (Box 13, Folder 8)
    By Guy A. Henry. Item is in English.
  - Item 52: Public Relations Suggested Reading, Publication (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Item 53: Five Points to Check Before you Make a Film, Publication (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Item 54: Patterns of Thinking, Publication (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Item 55: A workable idea for business-industry-education cooperation, Publication (Box 13, Folder 8)
    By Russell J. Darling. Item is in English.
  - Item 56: Press Relations for Conventions, Publication (Box 13, Folder 8)
    By J.J. Glasser. Item is in English.
  - Item 57: Summary of Principles of Sound Management, Publication (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Item 58: Trade Assocs. Which Engage in Labor Relations Activities, Publication (Box 13, Folder 8)
    By James D. Eggers. Item is in English.
  - Item 59: Observations on the Cement Case and the Rigid Steel Conduit Case, Publication (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Item 60: Dues Structures and Membership Procedures, Publication (Box 13, Folder 8)
    By Merill Maughan. Item is in English.
  - Item 61: Research, Publication (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Item 62: How to Put on a Successful Party for 12,000 Guests, Publication (Box 13, Folder 8)
    By Douglas Steinberg. Item is in English.
  - Item 63: Management's Responsibility in Labor Relations, Publication (Box 13, Folder 8)
    By Herman W. Steinkraus. Item is in English.
  - Item 64: Should Trade Assocs be Incorporated, Publication (Box 13, Folder 8)
    By Carl S. Whittier. Item is in English.
  - Item 65: Your Assoc and You, Publication (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Item 66: Personal Public Relations, Publication (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Item 67: Trade Assoc. Statistics, Publication (Box 13, Folder 8)
    By M.C. Dobrow. Item is in English.
  - Item 68: Commercial Surveys as an Aid in the Determination of Public Policy, Publication (Box 13, Folder 8)
    By Samuel P. Hayes, Jr. Item is in English.
  - Item 69: City Editor Gives the Lowdown, Publication (Box 13, Folder 8)
    By Dan Valetine. Item is in English.
  - Item 70: Trade Assoc. Management as a Career, Publication (Box 13, Folder 8)
    By Chester C. Kelsey. Item is in English.
  - Item 71: Trade Associations, Publication (Box 13, Folder 8)
    By John Moninger. Item is in English.
  - Item 72: Information for American Businessmen on the Marshall Plan, Publication (Box 13, Folder 8)
    By Office of Information - Economic Cooperation Administration. Item is in English.
  - Item 73: More Money for Assoc. Secretaries, Publication (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Item 74: Delivering Pricing and the Cement Case, Publication (Box 13, Folder 8)
    By W. Simon. Item is in English.
  - Item 75: There is no more terrible thing, Publication (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Item 76: Convention Delegate Expenditures, Publication (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Item 77: The Civic Responsibilities of Trade Assoc. Execs, Publication (Box 13, Folder 8)
    By Charles E. Boyd. Item is in English.
  - Item 78: New and Promising Activities, Publication (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Item 79: Remarks before the Advisory Council on Federal Reports, Publication (Box 13, Folder 8)
    By James E. Webb. Item is in English.
  - Item 80: When to Use Pictorial Symbols, Publication (Box 13, Folder 8)
    By F. Jahnel. Item is in English.
  - Item 81: Trade Assoc. Practices and Antitrust Law, Publication (Box 13, Folder 8)
    By Harvard Business Review. Item is in English.
  - Item 82: Men who won't stand still, Publication (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Item 83: Membership Manual, Publication (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Item 84: Some Fundamentals of Trade Assoc. Financing, Publication (Box 13, Folder 8)
    By Henry P. Fowler. Item is in English.
  - Item 85: Labor Relation Activities, Publication (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Item 86: Financing and Budgeting, Publication (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Item 87: Comment on Text Material for Classroom Discussion, Publication (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Item 88: Organization and Conduct of State and Local Assocs., Publication (Box 13, Folder 8)
    By Chantry W. Davis. Item is in English.
  - Item 89: The Public's Stake, Publication (Box 13, Folder 8)
    By Wilmoth C. Mack. Item is in English.
  - Item 90: Parliamentary Procedure, Publication (Box 13, Folder 8)
    By Kenneth G. Hance. Item is in English.
  - Item 91: The Hallmarks of a Good Convention, Publication (Box 13, Folder 8)
    By Walter Mitchell, Jr. Item is in English.
  - Item 92: Be Your Own Public Relations Counsel, Publication (Box 13, Folder 8)
    By Fredrick W. Bertram. Item is in English.
  - Item 93: Permissible Association Activities Under Anti-Trust Laws, Publication (Box 13, Folder 8)
    By E.B. Kixmiller. Item is in English.
- Box: 13, Folder: 9 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: The Standard Examination for Transit Employees, Publication (Box 13, Folder 9)
    By Glen U. Cleeton. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Placement Interview, Publication (Box 13, Folder 9)
    By Robert F. Royster. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Selection and Employment, Publication (Box 13, Folder 9)
    By Merwyn A. Kraft. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: The Personal Reaction Test, Publication (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Item 5: The American Transit Motor Ability Test, Publication (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Box: 13, Folder: 10 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Careers in Trucking Companies, Publication (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Item 2: Personnel Practices SurveyCarrier Vacation Policies, Publication (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Item 3: Personnel Practices SurveyGeneral Office Leave Policies, Publication (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Item 4: Truck Driver Hauls Special Cargo, Publication (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Item 5: Join the Proud Crowd, Publication (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Item 6: A Service Organization, Publication (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Item 7: Occupational outlook for truck and bus mechanics, Publication (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Item 8: Careers in the Trucking Industry, Publication (Box 13, Folder 10)
    By Jerry Buckman. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Employment outlook for driving occupations, Publication (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Item 10: Riding with Indian Scout, Publication (Box 13, Folder 10)
    By Robert G. Beason. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Free Teaching Aids, Publication (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Item 12: Wage and Salary Administration Materials, Publication (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Item 13: Cooperative Education, Publication (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Item 14: Transportation Courses, Publication (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Item 15: Trucking Industry Careers, Publication (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Item 16: The Chips are Down!, Publication (Box 13, Folder 10)
    By John V. Lawrence. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: Organization Chart and National Headquarters Staff, Publication (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Item 18: Noerr Motor Freight, Inc. v. Eastern Railroad Opinion, Publication (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Item 19: How to Keep from Growing Old, Publication (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Item 20: Outlook for the Motor Carrier Industry, Publication (Box 13, Folder 10)
    By Neil J. Curry. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: Invitation to Fifth Annual National Forum on Trucking Industrial Relations, Publication (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Item 22: Transportation Today, Publication (Box 13, Folder 10)
    By Guy W. Rutland, Jr. Item is in English.
  - Item 23: Labor Management Study Committees and Collective Bargaining, Publication (Box 13, Folder 10)
    By Walter L. Tompkins. Item is in English.
  - Item 24: The Ton-Mile, Does it Properly Measure Transportation Output?, Publication (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Item 25: What we can do for you and your company, Publication (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Item 26: Collective Bargaining in the Trucking Industry, Publication (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Item 27: An Informal Report to Truck Owners with Respect to ATA, Publication (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Item 28: Health Insurance Benefits for non-union employees, Publication (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Item 29: Occupational outlook for truck and bus mechanics, Publication (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Item 30: Employment outlook for driving occupations, Publication (Box 13, Folder 10)
- Box: 13, Folder: 11 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: A Guide to Company Fair Employment Practice Policy Statements, Publication (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Item 2: Trucking Past and Present, Publication (Box 13, Folder 11)
    By Oda Lindemann. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: American Trucking Trends, Publication (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Item 4: American Trucking Trends, Publication (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Item 5: American Trucking Trends, Publication (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Item 6: American Trucking Trends, Publication (Box 13, Folder 11)
- Box: 13, Folder: 12 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Scholarship Programs, Publication (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Item 2: Employee Communications Theme of 14th Annual National Forum, Publication (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Item 3: Applying Equal Employment in Trucking, Publication (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Item 4: Railroad Poverty?, Publication (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Item 5: Teaching Aids, Publication (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Item 6: Truck Drivers' Dictionary, Publication (Box 13, Folder 12)
- Box: 13, Folder: 13 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Safety Rules, Publication (Box 13, Folder 13)
    By H.F. Bousquet. Item is in English.
- Box: 13, Folder: 14 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Manual of Interpretations, Publication (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Item 2: Welcome Home Veterans, Publication (Box 13, Folder 14)
    By Fred Kraft. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Answering Your Questions about the Proposal Plan, Publication (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Item 4: Proposal Plan, Publication (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Item 5: Safety, Publication (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Item 6: Group Insurance Protection for You, Publication (Box 13, Folder 14)
- Box: 14, Folder: 1 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: By-Laws and Articles of Incorporation, Publication (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Dedicated to the principle, Publication (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: AVA Time Capsule, Publication (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Program Promotion Materials, Publication (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: Make a Commitment, Publication (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: An Inside Look, Publication (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: You're a Student?, Publication (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Item 8: Policy Resolutions, Publication (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Item 9: Handbook, Publication (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Item 10: Serving Vocational Education, Publication (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Item 11: By-Laws, Publication (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Item 12: Your Professional Commitment Builds the Skills of America, Publication (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Item 13: The Advisory Committee, Publication (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Item 14: Strategies for Action, Publication (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Box: 14, Folder: 2 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Group Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Retirement Income Plan for Salaried Employees, Publication (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Wage Chronology No. 1, Publication (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Box: 14, Folder: 3 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Why the Hatch Act is Worth Keeping - The Washington Post, Publication (Box 14, Folder 3)
    By Majorie G. Bribourg. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Hatch Act, Publication (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Box: 14, Folder: 4 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Job Evaluation and Merit Rating, Publication (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Box: 14, Folder: 5 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Burlington Northern News; Vol. 2 No. 10, Publication (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: Summary of Remarks, Publication (Box 14, Folder 5)
    By John C. Kohl. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Trains Running Late; Corrective Legislation Asked, Publication (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: Financial Results of Principal AMTRAK Routes, Publication (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: Employee Assistance Program, Publication (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Box: 14, Folder: 6 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Now get a car for a week on us on Amtrak's Special Florida Offer - Advertisement in Chicago Tribune, Publication (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: Transport News; Vol. 1, No. 2, Publication (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: Federal Railroad Administration, Publication (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Item 4: National Rail Passenger System, Publication (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Item 5: Memo for release, Publication (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Item 6: Memo re. new uniforms w photograph, Publication (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Item 7: Memo re. new uniforms w photograph, Publication (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Item 8: Amtrak Deep in Debt - The New York Times, Publication (Box 14, Folder 6)
    By Robert Linsdey. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Think of Our Metroliner as a Plane that never leaves the ground, Publication (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Item 10: Cub Scout Group Rides on One of 'Pan's' Last Trips, Publication (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Item 11: Rail Unions Fight Cuts in Passes, Publication (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Item 12: AMTRAK Adjustment in Offing, Publication (Box 14, Folder 6)
    By Robert M. Lewin. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Amtrak Slates Service for Cleveland on Word of 3-State Guarantee, Publication (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Item 14: Court Ruling Forces Pennsy to Continue Inter-City Service, Publication (Box 14, Folder 6)
    By Frank McDevitt. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Miles City, Mont. Mourns End of Passenger Trains, Publication (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Item 16: Final Whistle Blows on Dearborn Station, Publication (Box 14, Folder 6)
    By Fred Frailey. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: Current Developments Section No. 71, Publication (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Item 18: Current Developments Section No. 75, Publication (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Item 19: Gale McGee's Senate Summary, Publication (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Item 20: AMTRAK Photograph, Publication (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Item 21: Fact Sheet - Metropark, Publication (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Item 22: Railpax Hires Challenged AD Firm - The Washington Post, Publication (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Item 23: AMTRAK Press Release re. substantial ridership increases, Publication (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Item 24: AMTRAK Press Release re. Board of Directors of the National Railroad Passenger Co., Publication (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Item 25: Career ApparelIt's History and Psychology, Publication (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Item 26: May of Garden State Metropark Station, Publication (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Item 27: Key Dates of Washington-New York Rail Demonstration, Publication (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Item 28: Garden State Metropark Railroad Station Fact Sheet, Publication (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Item 29: Press Release - New Jersey Department of Transportation re. Metropark Dedication, Publication (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Item 30: AMTRAK Press Release re. Vacation program that includes free use of a 1972 air-conditioned automobile for a week, Publication (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Item 31: Transpo News Press Release re. Man in Motion exhibit, Publication (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Item 32: Summary Report to Stockholders, Publication (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Item 33: AMTRAK Press Release re. experimental tri-weekly train service, Publication (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Item 34: AMTRAK Press Release re. appointments for top positions in company, Publication (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Item 35: AMTRAK News Feature re. renaming of trains, Publication (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Item 36: AMTRAK Press Release re. improved scheduling, Publication (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Item 37: AMTRAK Press Release re. changes to inner-city passenger service, Publication (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Item 38: Press Release - New Jersey Department of Transportation re. Metropark Park and Ride, Publication (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Item 39: Press Release - New Jersey Department of Transportation re. Metropark Station, Publication (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Item 40: AMTRAK Press Release re. changes to inner-city passenger fares - 2 Copies, Publication (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Item 41: AMTRAK Press Release re. First Nationwide AD Campaign, Publication (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Item 42: AMTRAK Press Release re. Fall and Winter Timetable, Publication (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Item 43: News Feature - See America First, Publication (Box 14, Folder 6)